(The 1st Innocent Moo-Ku Fall Field Day)
("Fall Field Day of I Live Alone Goes Viral, Ranked 1st")
("Hyun Moo and Sung Hwan's Joke Comes True")
(Hyun Moo and Sung Hwan...)
(set it up themselves.)
(This episode had the largest number of cast members participating.)
(What are they doing over there?)
(We'll divide into Team Moo and Team Ku.)
(Team Moo with strong teamwork)
(Team Ku with many athletes)
(The CEO of MBC sent them impressive prizes too.)
(Game 1: The tug of war)
(Cheering)
(Dragging)
(Jang Woo's cheering strategy led Team Moo to the perfect victory.)
(Team Moo: 1, Team Ku: 0)
(Determined to win)
(Game 2: Move the Flour)
(Flashing the whites of his eyes)
(Exploding)
(I was crying watching this game. It was hilarious.)
(I couldn't control my laughter while watching this.)
(I've never laughed so hard lately. It was so funny.)
(Team Moo: 1, Team Ku: 1)
(Special Match: The 100m race)
(Jaw-dropping)
(Do you think I'm going to lose?)
(Going wild)
(We're a pretty wild bunch too.)
(Mr. Monkey, run!)
(But MINHO was bound to win anyway.)
(It was time to eat after such intense races.)
(The Korean Food War between...)
(Na Rae of Jeolla Province and KEY of Gyeongsang Province)
(She even brought a cutting board for cold pork slices.)
(They also got to enjoy a braised crab each.)
(Sweet)
- Do you want to try it? - Yes.
(They shared their boxed meals with each other.)
- Right. - That's it.
(They were fully refreshed.)
- Great. - Before the team match,
let's do one more special match.
- There are so many special matches. - Nice.
How come there are more special matches...
- than regular games? - Special matches.
There are so many special matches.
Didn't we do about 350 special matches?
I'm looking forward to this match the most today.
- What is it? - What is it?
It's ssireum!
(Another special match, ssireum)
How can anyone win when there's Sung Hwan?
You weigh more than me!
What are you talking about? What about my weight?
- I'm getting married soon. - Jang Woo,
- Why did you bring that up? - you weigh 4kg more than me.
Jang Woo.
I'd love to see a match between Sung Hwan and Jang Woo.
Will our scores be added to our team score?
The team score? It's an individual match.
- It's an individual match. - A match for the rice.
Woo Il.
I'd like to see you go up against Kian84.
- We're in the same weight class. - They must be in the same class.
- Right. - That's right.
- I wanted Dae Ho for my opponent. - By the way,
- I'm injured. - We need to give it a try.
- I'm injured. - No?
MINHO and Ji Hyeon should have a match.
- MINHO... - Right, those two.
- MINHO and Ji Hyeon. Yes. - Yes. MINHO and Ji Hyeon.
- How about KEY and Ju Seung? - Great.
(How about KEY and Ju Seung?)
- My gosh! - That's going to be fun.
- That's good. - They should have a match.
- That's going to be fun. - Dae Ho and Ja Yeon?
- Dae Ho and Ja Yeon? - Dae Ho and Ja Yeon?
(Getting worked up)
- She grabbed my sweatshirt. - She grabbed your sweatshirt.
- Only he's going to like that. - Dae Ho and Ja Yeon.
- Yes. - That sounds like fun.
At least one of them will be happy.
Look at the energy in his eyes.
Let's place the mats in the center.
We can put six mats down.
We worked so well together like a well-oiled machine.
Jang Woo. Sung Hwan. Put it on.
- We're starting with a big match. - Yes.
- Do you know how to put it on? - We'll start with a big match.
(We'll start with a big match.)
We're starting with a big match.
- We'll start with a big match. - Big Men's Match.
The match of the giants.
They only had each other to go up against.
- Right. - Yes.
Weight classes are so important...
- in ssireum. Of course. - Right.
It's for the Paektu Champion.
I'll tell you how to put on a satba once you're on the mat.
- Yes. - I see.
How do the announcers know...
how to put on a satba?
It's because announcers also work as commentaries for ssireum matches.
- Dae Ho knows how to put it on too. - All right. Are they ready?
Both of them weigh 102kg.
Jang Woo's weight is 102.9kg. My weight is 102.1kg.
It's a match of men with a three-digit weight?
- Getting up will be harder. - Put your shoulders together.
- That will be tough. - This will be fun to watch.
Gosh, I'm curious.
(Curious)
Gosh, they're so big.
- This will be fun. - Yes, this will be fun.
- This will be fun. - They're in the heavyweight class.
(The match of the heavyweight class will rock the world.)
Here it goes.
- My goodness. - He's a strong guy.
- He has the body of a champion. - Yes.
That's Sung Hwan.
Ku Ho Dong.
(Kung Fu Panda, Ku Ho Dong)
- He's so strong. - Yes.
- Pressing on the shoulders... - But Jang Woo is strong too.
- He's Lee Man Gi. - Gosh.
(The first member in the heavyweight class)
- Why did they use that clip? - Fat people are all yaks?
(An enraged yak)
(The destroyer of walnuts)
"The destroyer of walnuts."
Jang Man Gi.
- Gosh, there's so much tension. - Right.
Hey, why is there so much tension?
- On your feet. - My gosh.
- Jang Woo is super strong. - My gosh.
- Your shoulders. - They're like Paektu Champions.
(The mats seem too small for the aura of Paektu Champions.)
This is it. It was the rival match of the century.
Get ready.
(The rival match of the century will decide the strongest man.)
It's like a professional match.
(Even the slightest touch can be deadly to each other.)
- The Paektu Championship. - Set,
- Here it goes. - go.
- Look at the buffaloes. - Here it goes.
(The beasts fiercely butt their heads from the get-go.)
(Shocked)
Go.
He flung him over. He lifted Jang Woo. Look.
That's crazy.
(He wins with a powerful bear hug throw.)
(Ku Ho Dong roars.)
He couldn't put up a fight.
- Hey, we had no idea. - My gosh.
- It happened so fast. - Gosh, he's different.
Sung Hwan is the winner.
(Ku Sung Hwan wins the Paektu Championship.)
- Sung Hwan was so strong. - The bear hug throw.
Next up are Ju Seung and KEY.
- I see. This match is... - Right away?
- between kids. - This match looks safe.
- The lightweight class. - All right.
- The ssireum match of the kids. - The lightweight class.
The young ssireum wrestlers.
Hey, Ki Bum. You look like a kid.
Good luck.
- The kid ssireum wrestlers. - All right. Ssireum prodigies.
Ssireum prodigies.
- The winner will get a badge. - The winner gets a badge.
- The Well Done Badge. - Did you grab it?
- Yes. - I bet...
Ki Bum doesn't even know the ssireum rules.
- He probably doesn't at all. - I don't.
I've never wrestled ssireum in my life.
Ki Bum, just dance.
On your feet.
Do the choreography of "like JENNIE."
- Ju Seung at least works out. - Just do the steps.
Set, go.
(Back and forth)
- My gosh. - All right.
Well...
No. Not that.
I'm sorry.
- Give it to me now. - "You fool."
(They are identical.)
"You fool."
- They were so adorable. - That's crazy.
You got it.
(The aunts and uncles have a blast at their talent show.)
I told those kids not to fight.
Hey!
(This is a do-or-die moment for them.)
What was Ju Seung doing?
(Two white swans dance all over the ssireum mats.)
Look at KEY. He can hold out.
Hey!
(Pushing)
Get lost.
(Flinging him down)
- He shoved Ju Seung. - Hey, you can't lose.
- Hey, he did it. This was fun. - Gosh, how adorable.
- Hey. - Wait.
I won?
- You won. - I did?
- He... - He was surprised.
- He didn't even know he won. - You won.
Even when I was wrestling,
I was quite puzzled.
- You could freely move him around. - Yes.
- "What are we doing?" - That makes him a paper doll.
- You should break wooden boards. - You're quite strong.
That guy...
- Is he really a martial artist? - He's strong.
I'm strong.
I thought you two were doing ballroom dance.
- Hey. - It was fun.
- KEY... - One, two.
Look at his steps. So flashy.
(Doing a flash dance to celebrate)
- It's the contrary. - It's another big match.
The Taebaek Championship.
- All right. Squat down. - This will be fun.
- Okay. - Gosh.
"Bacterrius?"
The thing is, Kian84 is strong.
Actually, Kian84 has grit.
(There can't be any germ in my house.)
(The embodiment of cleanliness, the bleach rocker)
He looks like a Mongolian wrestler.
I can tell that he has a strong frame.
(The expert at cultivating bacteria)
(The king of bacteria breeders, Bacterrius)
Gosh, they're so serious.
Press your shoulders against each other's.
(It's time to determine who has the real rocker spirit.)
- Press them against each other's. - Put your shoulders together.
- All right. - There you go.
- I didn't get why they did that. - Okay.
Don't do that.
- What are you two doing? - What are you doing?
Are you two in love?
- What are they doing? - Are you in love?
- What are you doing? - Do you like it that much?
- Kian84. - Why did you open your mouth?
- He kept... - You can't do that.
- He's kissing Woo Il's ear. - His ear...
- What are you doing? - Look at him.
(Appalled)
- This was no joke. - What an awful sight.
(Opening his mouth)
- Come on. - That wasn't the vibe.
- Yes, it was. - Why were you feeling each other?
- Wait. - Wait.
- They keep touching each other! - My gosh. Oh, no!
Why were you feeling each other?
(What an unpleasant sight.)
- Why do you keep fumbling? - Come on.
- Why are you doing this? - Why do you keep fumbling?
(Fumbling for the satba)
- They keep touching each other. - What are you doing?
(Or fumbling for love?)
Why did they do that?
What are you doing? That's gross!
- Their shoulders are together! - What are they doing?
- Referee! Check on them. - My gosh.
What are you doing?
(Looking provocative)
Come on.
They keep fumbling like this.
- Why do you keep wedging your chin? - On your feet.
- Okay. - Get ready, set...
- No. - Not yet.
Why did they put their bodies together?
(How improper!)
(Terrified)
- My gosh. - Goodness.
- He's strong. - He pulled in like this.
- Here we go. - Get ready, set...
- He pulled in like this. - Right.
- Go. - Here we go.
(The match begins.)
- That's it. Hold out. - Hold out.
- Anyone could win. - It was a tight match.
I could feel that Woo Il was giving his all.
Anyone could win.
- Don't press with your chin. No. - His chin!
- Don't press with your chin. - Hey!
No. You can't do that. That's not allowed.
- Don't press with your chin. No. - His chin!
- Don't press with your chin. - Hey!
(I will now begin disinfecting Bacterrius.)
Yes. This is what makes...
- amateur ssireum fun. - Of course.
(Feeling refreshed)
Come on. Are you a woodpecker?
(Clean, fresh, and confident!)
That's just crazy.
- It's all about endurance. - He's got energy left.
- Wait, your chin. - It's almost...
He only lost because Woo Il used up his energy.
Kian84 kept pressing his chin on him.
- He lost. - That was an impressive match!
- That was fun. - It was a match of crazy love.
"Crazy love?"
- Crazy love. - Well done.
My chin ached when I was eating afterward.
Then imagine how it must've hurt for Woo Il.
This is the main match of the day.
- MINHO versus Park Ji Hyeon! - Yes!
(Park Ji Hyeon versus Choi MINHO)
- There's always another main match. - Redeem yourself from the race.
- There's always another main match. - Another big match.
- All right. Let's go. - MINHO.
- Here it goes. - They were also rivals.
- They look determined too. - My gosh.
(The unpredictable rival match)
(They're just as competitive as the other.)
This will be fun.
Ji Hyeon weighs 10kg...
- more than him. - Really?
- On your feet. - Let's see.
- Their gaze changed. - Not yet.
- It's the Kumgang Championship. - It's another big match.
You have to pull.
- Pull him to you once it starts. - All right.
- Let's go! - Pull him to you once it starts.
- Let's go! - Pull him toward you.
He's ready to become a hero.
(Hero Park Ji Hyeon sets out.)
(I will defeat you, Fiery Man.)
- All right. - Pull him toward you.
- Let's go! - See? His gaze changed.
(Do you think I'm going to lose?)
(Everyone knows him as the workout maniac.)
He's crazy for it.
(Iron Man Choi MINHO)
(I'll rule the world of ssireum too.)
- Great. - Let's go!
Their postures were the best.
They should look like a table when they get up.
- Set, go! Pull your left hand. - They're different.
(They measure each other's strength intensely from the start.)
- My gosh. - Hey.
Their postures are great.
- They were taking this seriously. - My gosh.
(MINHO uses his strength to hold out.)
That's how their postures should look.
(It's my turn now!)
(MINHO goes for the inner leg hook.)
(Ji Hyeon fights back with the counter throw.)
MINHO made his move first.
- Ji Hyeon... Right. He did. - He did the counter throw.
Ji Hyeon used MINHO's strength against him.
(Fiery Charisma has fallen!)
MINHO told me what it was like afterward.
He tried to get Ji Hyeon to move,
- but Ji Hyeon didn't even budge. - Right.
Ji Hyeon is really strong.
Gosh, MINHO lost.
I bet he's boiling with anger on the inside.
MINHO is upset.
What does this mean?
Gosh. What do we do?
(Gosh, I ended up beating him.)
- He's walking on eggshells. - Gosh.
- He's powerful. - Can't we do this with a smile?
Doesn't it hurt? It hurts, right?
- It's fine. - Really?
- I used the falling technique. - Okay. The falling technique.
The falling technique?
- What did he do? - He used the falling technique.
That was so lame.
- Seriously. - He used the falling technique.
He could've just said, "Ji Hyeon is better."
Ji Hyeon is the winner!
(Park Ji Hyeon wins the Kumgang Championship.)
You're so strong.
Grab the satba.
Park Ji Hyeon versus Ahn Jae Hyeon!
- Their postures look great. - Anyone could win.
- They're in the same weight class. - It's anyone's game.
Their weight is identical.
- They're exactly the same. - Yes, they are.
He's gotten muscular...
- after he started to work out. - He's gotten strong.
(There's no more Pale Man.)
Park Ji Hyeon.
(Hoisting up)
Gosh, he was so good.
Now.
Park Ji Hyeon is the winner!
- Ji Hyeon is great. - My gosh.
It makes sense. Ji Hyeon is a great wrestler!
- Gosh, that's just so petty. - The one who beat him...
ought to win for him to save face.
Kang Yong was the commentator.
- Why did he suddenly participate? - I don't know.
- Right. - He was wearing a suit.
So we told him not to, but he still went for it.
Actually, to me, he was the MVP of the day.
- Same here. - The MVP.
Kang Yong isn't an easy opponent.
- Look how strong he is. - All right. Great.
- Yes. - My gosh.
- Great. Yes. - He just lifted Kang Yong.
Ji Hyeon is so good.
- Seriously. - All right.
We should have included that as the official game.
I knew it. A trot singer ought to be good at ssireum.
(Singing a trot song)
What? That was random.
- It's unconditional - It's unconditional
(Happily singing a trot song after winning 3 matches in a row)
(Excited)
What's wrong with his eyes?
(I'll run to you when you call for me)
(I'll run to you no matter what)
(Celebrating his series of wins with a fun song)
- Thank you. - Okay.
- This is how it's done. - He's a trot singer indeed.
- You're so cool. - All right.
There he comes!
(Walking up)
- A cow is entering. - There comes a golden cow.
(Cheering)
(The roar of the ultimate beast)
He's the final boss.
Ji Hyeon, show him!
Ji Hyeon, show him your celebratory act.
(Growling)
- Great. - Good luck.
- Ji Hyeon, you can beat him. - Techniques...
You can totally beat him.
He's going to make history.
It's the legendary match.
(The final ssireum match is finally set.)
- This is for the first champion. - He's so big.
- There's no way he can win. - Okay. On your feet.
We must pick our champion.
Start when I say, "go."
(He defeated Giant Lee Jang Woo with one throw.)
- That was crazy. - It was crazy.
(Beast Ku Sung Hwan)
(He beat MINHO, Jae Hyeon, and Kang Yong with one move.)
He beat everyone including Jae Hyeon and Kang Yong.
- Sung Hwan only remained. - Yes.
Park Ji Hyeon is the winner!
(However, only one man can be the ultimate champion.)
- The weight difference is 22kg. - Right.
- There's no way he can win. - Gosh, no way.
- Get ready, - When you start,
- set, go. - shift your weight back.
- Here it goes. - Just don't let him lift you.
- Get ready, - When you start,
- set, go. - Shift your weight back.
Here it goes.
(There will be no mercy in this match of the century.)
- Watch. - My gosh.
(Who will come out victorious?)
- Just don't let him lift you. - Get ready.
- Get ready, - When you start,
- set, go. - shift your weight back.
Here it goes.
- My gosh. - What?
- Okay. - Watch.
(Sung Hwan throws Ji Hyeon over as soon as they begin.)
- I knew it. - It's impossible.
- There's nothing he can do. - There's just no way.
Hooray!
- Don't be so happy, Sung Hwan. - You have no control over this.
(Thanking Ji Hyeon for being a good friend)
This is...
- It was embarrassing. - Right.
Our first ssireum champion is Ku Sung Hwan.
(The First Rainbow Champion, Ku Sung Hwan)
He wins the 20kg of rice!
(Hooray for the champion, Ku Sung Hwan)
He's a champion indeed.
- He's so good. - He really is.
- Ju Seung. - One, two, three.
- This one. - Let's go.
Everyone helped out and cleaned up so fast afterward.
All these students are so sweet.
It was so fun to watch ssireum. I had a blast.
- Stand it up? - We can stand it up and lug it.
- I see. This is the net? - Yes, that's the net.
- What's this? - This must be the net.
- How far should I go? - Yes.
- The net? - That's the net.
We'll finally get to watch it.
- The wretched game is starting. - Exactly.
All right. We'll play a team sport next.
- Okay. - It's super volleyball.
Super volleyball.
That's so cute.
There comes a dugong.
As for the team scores, we're tied with 1 to 1.
There are no special matches.
- Okay. - We'll have team matches.
Let's do the 3-3-2 formation.
- The 3-3-2 formation. - Okay.
- We can let it bounce once. - Just once.
- This? - For now.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- We got this! - Let's do this.
(They are more determined to win the match.)
Gosh, I really wanted us to win this match.
- Here it goes. - Here it goes. Go!
That's it.
Here it goes. Go! That's it.
- One. - That was great!
- No. - She was good.
- No. - There you go.
Great. One more. Go for it.
- Block it. - Do it together.
That was great.
- Hey! - Get it.
- Okay. - Hit it back.
What's happening?
- It's out. - Does it count? What's going on?
- No. - There he goes.
- It's out. - This counts!
- This counts! Bring it back. - It's out.
(We can make this work!)
That's the Hoop Boy.
This counts!
The Hoop Boy must be as old as him now.
- Give it to me. - Yes.
- Bring it back! - Strike it hard.
If you can bring it back, we'll allow it.
- No. - We'll allow it if they can do it.
- They tried so hard. - It's over.
Woo Il is so funny.
- He hit it like a seal. - My gosh. That's hilarious.
- He looked like a seal. - It was the wind.
He hit it like a seal.
- That was funny. - It's 1 to 0.
- I'm here. - Ji Hyeon should... Okay.
- Like this? Okay. - Okay.
I'll stay on the side.
Only heartless people would criticize him for that.
Seriously. That was really cool.
- Let's go, Woo Il. - Let's go.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- Okay. The formation looks good. - Let's begin.
(CODE KUNST will serve again.)
- His serves were great. - Let's go!
Let's go. There you go.
- Okay. - Ki Bum was great at this game.
Ki Bum is quick at reacting.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Hit it back. - I got it.
Go.
- Great. - Keep it going!
- Why... - Okay. Here it goes!
(Go to Team Ku's court.)
(Woo Il blocks the shot.)
(With Woo Il's block, their counterattack goes through.)
- Yes. - Yes!
It didn't go over.
(I blocked the shot successfully.)
- I know. - We got this.
It's 1 to 1.
- Let's go, MINHO. - Great.
- Okay. - There you go!
- Yes! - Yes!
(MINHO delivers a powerful serve.)
(Jang Woo receives it.)
(Jang Woo hits it back again.)
(Jang Woo hits it for the third time.)
- One more time. - It's coming back.
- It's coming. - Hit it high.
- Hit it high. - Hang in there.
- Wait, it's ours again. - No.
The wind that day...
It kept blowing to one side.
- What's going on? - No!
- It's over? - Yes!
(Slippery)
- Nice, Jang Woo. - Yes!
- We must switch after this set. - Okay.
It went back that way again.
(They switch sides despite the heavy rain.)
- We must send it far. - We must push it back.
- Right. We should do that first. - Push it. Don't hit it.
- Make it go far. - Push it up like this.
I'll try my best to send it to the net.
Go.
(They resume the game after switching the courts.)
- There you go. It went over. - Great!
He's really good at anything with a ball.
- Send it to the net. Yes. - To the net!
- To the net! - Send it to me.
That's good. It's mine.
- Okay. Hit it over. - Okay!
(I'm Fiery MINHO.)
- Okay. - Gosh, look at MINHO's shot.
- There. Hit it back! - Okay.
- MINHO, hit it over. Yes. - Okay.
(They're engaged in a fierce battle.)
- Slowly. - I'm blocking it!
- I'm blocking it! - Slowly.
- Great, Woo Il. - Gosh.
- Nice. - Nice, Woo Il.
(Teeth clenching)
(The blocking expert is here.)
Mine!
(Mine Kian84 has come to defeat the blocking expert.)
To the net! That's it. Get it!
Ja Yeon was as good as Kim Yeon Koung.
- I got it. - Hey.
Okay!
(The guardian of Team Ku, Ok Ja Yeon Koung)
- My gosh. Wait. - No!
- Ki Bum was great. - Mine!
- Great job. - Hit it over.
- Push it. - Great job.
Darn it.
- Slowly. - It went over.
- This is a long rally. - It keeps going.
- Nice. - Get that.
(It seems the match is nearing its end, )
(but it isn't.)
- Great job. - Okay.
Is this how it's supposed to be?
- Is this how it's supposed to be? - Are you okay?
It's pouring down. Is this how it's supposed to be?
It was just a game.
- But we were so determined to win. - It was just a game.
Right. That's exactly how I felt too.
When I was playing, I wondered,
"Why am I doing this?"
- The moment that crossed my mind, - We tried really hard to win.
This also popped into my head for the first time.
- "Why am I dying to beat them?" - Right.
- That's why sports are fun. - Yes.
All of a sudden, I wanted to win this game no matter what.
- We wanted to win too. - We feel it when we start playing.
So one of us has to die for this game to end, right?
Look at the color of everyone's lips.
Then why don't we make this our last point?
No.
Let's make it our last point.
- One last point. - Okay.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors for the serve.
- This will count as five points. - Okay.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Okay. We have to serve.
We were all going crazy then.
- We couldn't laugh about it later. - We couldn't.
- Gosh. - Are you all right?
End it with your serve.
- The wind is blowing. - CODE KUNST.
- Hey. - The ball got deflated so much.
This counts as five points.
- This counts as five points. - Okay.
- We must stay focused now. - It's windy.
- Why did we try so hard? - Hurry.
- Stay focused now. Ju Seung. Focus. - Yes.
- Right. - Look at everyone's gaze.
Look. She's praying.
- Is that allowed? - Voldemort? Seriously?
- She's praying. - I was losing it.
- It was our last round. - There you go!
We got this!
Let's go!
(We're staking our everything on this ball today.)
- All right. Slowly. Okay. - Let's go.
- All right. Slowly. Okay. - Okay.
- Why am I nervous for this? - You must hit it back together.
- We can't just push. - Okay.
- Everyone must help out. - Ki Bum.
All right.
- Right here. - Our skills improved.
- Right. Even when it was windy... - Mine.
- Okay. - Great job.
- Keep the ball in play. - Hey.
- It's over. - Wait.
(MINHO throws himself to keep the ball in play.)
- Keep the ball in play. - Hurry.
- Okay. That's it. - Slowly.
- Nice. - Kim Yeon Koung!
- We got this! - We got this!
- My gosh. - Gosh.
Look at that kid.
First of all, the ball is bigger than her.
(Team Ku wins the super volleyball match.)
That really hurt.
- We still did well. - Well done.
Are there more special matches?
- What? - Are there more special matches?
- That guy... - There are.
It was upsetting when we lost.
- Right. - Yes.
Losing this match upset us. That means...
- we gave it our all. - Right.
- Yes. - We were so eager to win.
If we didn't give it our all, we wouldn't have been upset.
- We bonded a lot over this game. - Right.
After playing this game, I felt closer to my team.
- It almost made me tear up. - My gosh. This game...
Playing sports together definitely helps you...
- bond with others. - Right.
Our rally continued for ten minutes.
- Right. We got better too. - It did.
- Our skills improved later. - But our fingers got so stiff...
- like in the movie, "The Exorcist." - Yes.
Your muscles were sore the next day, right?
Yes.
I got three massages this week.
I got an IV drip after that.
- Same here. - I couldn't lift my spoon.
(Regardless of the results, everyone enjoyed this fun match.)
- We did a great job. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - We let them win.
- Seriously. - We just let them win.
Our play was better, though.
- "Our play was better." - Our play was better.
He was right.
Before this game, I saw them as my opponents.
But after this game, I felt close to them.
- Let's have some snacks. - Snacks?
Let's do the next match fast and take the snacks home.
- Stop trying to take food home. - I want to use the toilet.
He kept trying to take food home.
Does anyone want chicken skewers?
Anyone?
I'll bring some.
(Panting)
Our youngest.
I should have chicken skewers.
- We're full. - Right.
But we'll still have some.
I must at least have a taste.
(Embracing each other's shoulders)
This is fun, though.
- It's so fun, isn't it? - Yes.
Why is this so fun? It's just a game.
- They've gotten so close. - They have.
They became good friends.
(They walk over to the food truck Moomoo arranged.)
(Sizzling)
I tasted a lot of food to settle on this food truck.
Gosh, they're freshly grilled.
It's so good. Try it.
- You should have it first. - It's okay.
- Thank you. - Sure.
(No matter how full I am, I can't say no to this.)
(Humming)
- It's good. - Yes, it's good.
So this is your first field day ever.
It's such a thrill.
- I'm having a great time. - This is a one-of-a-kind field day.
We had blue crabs.
It's almost impossible to find a field day as fun as this.
- Right. - Of course.
That's true.
Guys.
(Spacing out)
- Everyone was getting tired. - Yes.
(The intense activities have exhausted them.)
- They're hot. - Are they chicken skewers?
- Fathermoo. - Yes.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Thank you for the food, Fathermoo.)
It was really tasty.
- Gosh, Kang Yong. - My goodness.
(Taking a bite)
(Restoring their energy thanks to Fathermoo)
All right. This is the last game.
- It's our last game. - Yes.
As for the score,
- it's 2 to 1. Team Ku is leading. - Yes.
(Team Moo won the tug of war with good teamwork.)
(Team Moo: 1, Team Ku: 0)
(Team Ku won a point with Move the Flour.)
(Team Moo: 1, Team Ku: 1)
(Team Ku wins the point with the exhausting volleyball game.)
(Team Moo: 1, Team Ku: 2)
(Team Ku snatches the lead.)
(The winning team will get Korean beef as a prize.)
- This game is worth 100 points. - My gosh.
The team that wins this game will win.
- This was our final goal. - So...
- Right. - We've been playing for this game.
- That's right. - It was all for this. Okay.
When will this rule change?
This is how a field day goes at every company.
- Right. - Yes.
Some people are injured. What about them?
They will be excluded from this game.
Raise your hand if you're injured.
But I should be participating.
(Sung Hwan and Dae Ho from Team Ku are injured.)
- Earlier... - Yes, I'm injured.
- He got hurt. - I pulled my hamstring.
If they're sitting this one out, I will do.
- Okay. Na Rae. - Okay.
- My ACL acts up on rainy days. - Team Ku steals the lead.
He pulled his hamstrings.
So the 1st 4 runners will run 100m.
Yes.
The last two runners...
will run 200m which is half a lap to finish the race.
- Okay? - Okay.
Okay.
(Ju Seung versus Jang Woo, Ja Yeon versus Lee Jung, )
(Kang Yong versus Woo Il, KEY versus Hyun Moo...)
- Then let's get ready. - Let's do it!
Hey, let's do the team cheer before we start.
- Let's do our cheer. - It's our last game!
- All right. - Let's go.
Everyone, you've all done a great job.
One, two, three.
- MINHO, MINHO, let's go! - Let's go!
"MINHO, MINHO, let's go."
Bring it in for our last victory.
- One, two, three. - Two, three.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- Moomoo Challenge! - Challenge!
It's been ages since I did a relay race.
When was the last time? Was it when I was in 12th grade?
(Zooming by)
Gosh, he was warming up.
- That's what he was doing? - Yes.
(On top of that, he even got changed proactively.)
I should run as fast as I can since it's our last game.
He changed his pants?
- I didn't know. - Me neither.
(Light)
(Leaving behind Fiery MINHO, )
(Ju Seung warms up rather enthusiastically.)
- Let's go, Ju Seung. - I just stay on this lane, right?
Jang Woo.
Let's take the beef home.
- I'll show you! - Let's take Korean beef home!
- Korean beef! - I'll show you.
I'll show you...
- how fast a fat guy can run. - Seriously.
He definitely surprised me.
- Seriously. What a surprise. - Actually, pigs are fast runners.
My hip joints are hurting like crazy.
I don't even know how I managed to be a dancer.
- Is this the spot? - Yes.
The two of them became very close.
If the distance is 100m, I can give it the last spurt.
- Kang Yong was fast. - Yes.
- You're so fast. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - Okay.
You never know what will happen.
- Are you ready? - Are you ready?
Yes!
- Let's go. - Let's do this.
- Here I go. - Good luck.
- Good luck. - Count down from three.
Good luck.
- It'll be, "3, 2, bang." - Good luck.
- All right. - Good luck.
- On your mark. - All right.
- Ju Seung is very agile. - You need to be ready.
Get ready.
Here they come.
The teams were evenly matched,
so I couldn't predict the result.
- We picked the runners that way. - Exactly.
That's right.
Two, three.
Lee Ju Seung!
Three.
(They set off!)
- Jang Woo! - Look at Jang Woo.
Look at him. His belly comes out first.
- Jang Woo! - Lee Ju Seung!
(The number 1 runners charge forward quickly.)
- They're good. - Hey, he's a good runner.
- You never know. - Ju Seung is a good runner.
- Lee Ju Seung! - Jang Woo!
(The two teams' cheering squads compete fiercely.)
- Hey, he's a good runner. - There he goes.
(The competition to take the lead is cutthroat.)
You never know.
- Jang Woo. - Jang Woo is good.
- Nice. There you go. - Jang Woo.
- What is Ju Seung doing? - What is he doing?
(The number 2 runners get ready to receive the baton.)
Let's go.
Ju Seung should take off his taekwondo uniform.
Ja Yeon had to go all the way to the front.
- Come on! - Jang Woo!
Hey, Lee Ju Seung!
- Give it properly! - My goodness!
- What a slowpoke. - Can't he do that right?
Hey, Lee Ju Seung!
- The baton. - Nice.
- Jang Woo! - Hey, Lee Ju Seung!
Lee Jung. Okay, that's good.
- Hey, that's good. Hey. - She's fast.
- Hey. - Lee Jung is fast.
- Let's go! - She's catching up.
She's catching up.
(Lee Jung takes the lead.)
- Hey. - Lee Jung is fast.
- Look at that. - She's fast.
She comes like a giraffe.
Lee Jung. Okay, that's good.
The outer lane is at a disadvantage.
- Hey. - Lee Jung is fast.
She's catching up.
- Ja Yeon is so fast. - She's catching up.
- She's fast. - She's so fast.
Ok Ja Yeon.
- She has caught up. - Lee Jung!
- Ja Yeon is so fast. - Lee Jung!
(She gets ahead in the speed of lightning.)
- She has caught up. - Lee Jung!
- Ja Yeon is so fast. - Lee Jung!
(Ja Yeon won't go easy on the younger member!)
Oh, my.
(The two of them do their best.)
I can't believe it.
(You're nearly there!)
Let's go!
(Thanks to Ja Yeon, Woo Il sets off first.)
He's fast.
(They pass the baton to the number 3 runners.)
- Come on! - Im Woo Il!
(It's incredible speed!)
Kang Yong was barefoot too.
- He couldn't wear his shoes. - His shoes were uncomfortable.
- Look. - Kang Yong is fast.
(He runs barefoot in his suit.)
- Kang Yong is fast. - There he goes.
- What's up with Kang Yong? - There he goes.
- Im Woo Il. - Woo Il.
(He gets ahead!)
What's up with Kang Yong?
He's fast.
- Look at him. - He got ahead in the outer lane.
Okay.
Kang Yong is fast.
KEY and I are next.
- He's fast. - There you go.
- KEY! - There you go.
- KEY! - Come on!
KEY, let's go!
(They pour out their energy to run at full speed.)
(It's a close match.)
- KEY. - No.
Hyun Moo is still fast.
- Hyun Moo is fast. - That's right.
He's getting closer.
(Neck-and-neck)
- They're neck-and-neck. - It's a close match.
- KEY, come on. - Hyun Moo, let's go.
(Number 5 runners need to run twice the distance.)
- There you go. - Come on.
- Run! - Come on.
(CODE KUNST gets the baton.)
- Come on. - Good luck.
- There they go. - Show us what you can do.
(Ji Hyeon picks up the speed.)
- Ji Hyeon is fast. - Ji Hyeon is fast.
There they go.
(There's a bit of distance between them.)
- CODE KUNST. - Show us what you can do.
- Good luck. - Ji Hyeon is fast.
- Ji Hyeon is fast. - My goodness.
CODE KUNST is good.
(That monkey is back.)
(A monkey climbs up a tree)
- Mr. Monkey. - Mr. Monkey.
- Mr. Monkey. - Mr. Monkey, run.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Do your best.
- Fight on. - You can do it.
- A bit longer. - "You can do it."
My goodness.
- CODE KUNST. - Ji Hyeon, let's go.
- He's fast. - There he goes.
CODE KUNST, show us.
- Fight on. - Ji Hyeon is fast.
- Ji Hyeon is fast. - CODE KUNST is fast too.
There goes CODE KUNST.
- He got ahead. - CODE KUNST is fast too.
There goes CODE KUNST. He got ahead.
(Mr. Monkey gets past the human.)
- CODE KUNST got ahead. - How did he do that?
There goes CODE KUNST. He got ahead.
(He quickly takes the inner lane.)
The best producer of the era, CODE KUNST!
He got ahead. They're going back and forth.
- He's fast. - CODE KUNST ran very well.
He can even climb a tree.
- You never know. - CODE KUNST.
- Let's go. - He got ahead.
- Let's go. - No, get him.
- He got ahead. - Ji Hyeon, get him.
(A long distance)
(Meanwhile, the last runners are on standby.)
The last runners.
(Shouting)
(The man who fell in love with running)
Kian84 is a runner.
- That's right. - Yes. He's the national runner.
MINHO is a singer.
He completed the New York Marathon.
(Runner84)
(Nervous)
(He's a workout enthusiast who surpasses genres.)
- He's nothing but a singer. - That's right.
- He only runs indoors. - That's right.
- That's right. - He's unfamiliar with the tracks.
- The real deal is different. - He works out as a hobby.
(Runner84 versus Iron Man)
- Let's go. - No, get him.
- No, he can do it. - Ji Hyeon, get him.
- No, he can do it. - He ran out of energy.
- Mr. Monkey. - Mr. Monkey.
- A bit more. - A bit more.
MINHO will close the distance.
- That was fast. - MINHO will get ahead.
Okay. Let's go.
(Runner84 versus Iron Man Who will be the final winner?)
No, he can do it.
Hey, run!
MINHO will get ahead.
No, he can do it.
Hey, run!
MINHO will get ahead.
No, he can do it.
- Hey, run! - Look at Kian84.
- Good. - He's so fast.
No way.
Kian84.
- No way. - MINHO.
- He's so fast. - He's so fast.
- No. - Kian84.
- Kian84 ran really well. - Kian84 runs every day.
- Kian84 is ahead by far. - Hey, run!
(Iron Man chases after the running man.)
Kian84.
- No way. - MINHO.
- He's so fast. - He's so fast.
- No. - Kian84.
- A bit more. - No.
- Kian84. - Kian84, run.
No.
(MINHO gets ahead.)
(I can't watch this!)
- Kian84, run. - No.
(My goodness)
I'm so annoyed.
Kian84 did well.
He's nothing but a singer.
Doesn't he work as an idol?
- Kian84 has... - Why...
- a marathoner's posture. - That's right.
- MINHO is a sprinter. - He has a sprinter's posture.
I mistakenly thought that it was 100m,
so I didn't breathe at first.
You hold your breath for a sprint.
You wanted to hold your breath.
I got a bit excited in the beginning and held my breath.
- After running for a while, - You began to hyperventilate.
I took a breath.
- Never mind. Anyway... - Listen.
- You never know. - You can hold your breath for 100m,
- but not 200m. - That's right.
- You even thought about breathing. - It's so...
- Never mind. I did well. - You're incredible.
Kian84.
(The distance between them lessens.)
- No. - Well done.
A bit more.
- Kian84. - Kian84, run.
- No! - Kian84!
(I can't watch this.)
Team Ku!
Come on!
(Struggling)
- No! - He's so fast.
Look at his facial expression. Look at the way he breathes.
(MINHO breathes nonstop.)
- Kian84, it's okay. - He runs like a machine.
The finish line.
- The finish line. - The finish line.
(We need to prepare the finish line.)
MINHO.
(Who will pass the finish line first?)
(They run at full speed until the end.)
All right.
(MINHO wins!)
- He entered with a smile. - Well done.
(Team Ku's MINHO came from behind and won.)
Well done.
- Oh, no. - He was upset.
- No. That's life, Kian84. - That's right.
Let me give one excuse.
- It's okay. - No!
- It's okay. - I mean...
It's okay to lose.
- It's okay. - Breathing...
You'll have another chance.
You did well.
I'm so annoyed.
Kian84.
- You're seven years older. - CODE KUNST is right.
I got so annoyed...
that I asked him, "What's your record for 10km?"
I was confident about running 10km.
- You'll win that race. - Of course.
"My record for 10km is 45 minutes."
He said, "My record is 39 minutes."
You couldn't win against him.
I can't beat him in anything.
He hasn't run a full marathon.
I bet he's much better than me at a full marathon.
- No way. - What are you talking about?
- Your running contains your life. - That's right.
- It's touching. - Yes.
- MINHO's running isn't touching. - I hate that more.
I'm so annoyed.
I feel bad.
That means I was the only one who beat MINHO.
In which event did you beat him?
- Sure, Hyun Moo. - Sprint.
He was out of energy.
(Team Ku wins the relay.)
- MINHO. - You were amazing.
- You didn't disappoint. - Okay.
- My goodness. - Nice.
Let's say, "MINHO, MINHO, let's go!"
- "MINHO, MINHO, let's go!" - Okay.
One, two, three.
- MINHO, MINHO, let's go! - MINHO, MINHO, let's go!
- Kian84. - You did well, Kian84.
He was too fast.
- He's upset. - He's upset.
You did well, Kian84.
- You did well, Kian84. - You did very well.
- It was a touching picture. - Yes.
- You did very well. - He was too fast.
- I feel bad. - Hey, you're a marathoner.
That's right.
- You're a marathoner. - Kian84 stayed close behind.
- Okay. - It was really cool.
It was cool.
(Kian84, get up.)
I should work out regularly.
(Mr. Monkey and Ji Hyeon support each other.)
- We lack the stamina, right? - Yes.
Mr. Monkey should get a banana as a bonus.
(Thank you.)
He needs a banana for his good work.
I ate it today as well.
It felt really nice then.
Ji Hyeon and I became very close through this event.
(MINHO approaches Kian84 1st.)
Kian84.
I'm sorry.
He's so annoying.
Seriously, MINHO.
The last event was for you.
Thus, at the First Innocent Moo-Ku Fall Field Day,
Team Ku won...
- the group relay race. - Okay.
Team Ku won.
(Team Ku becomes the final winner.)
- The first winning team. - Thank you.
(Coughing)
- Oh, my. - What's up with him?
- Are you okay? - He's practically dying.
- I'm okay. - You're okay, right?
I'm okay.
Now that everything is over, I feel a sense of camaraderie.
- I know. - Seriously. We became closer.
The field day was fun. It rained.
I'm in tears.
- Team Ku is today's winner. - Yes.
The members will receive the prize, the Korean beef set.
(The members will receive the prize, the Korean beef set.)
- Yes. - I'm jealous.
We ate Korean beef thanks to MINHO.
- That's right. - He's running again.
MINHO, thank you.
Take one each.
My goodness.
That should've been mine.
This is great.
- All right. - Who hasn't received one?
- That's the taste of fall. - Thank you.
It feels like a holiday.
- I'm sorry. - You did well.
- Why would you be sorry? - Seriously.
- Thank you. - Well done.
I'll enjoy the meat. Thank you.
The MVP will be chosen regardless of the team.
- We'll vote among ourselves. - Okay.
- I nominate MINHO. - MINHO.
- He did the best. - Well done.
MINHO.
- MINHO is an MVP candidate. - Yes.
- Who else? - I personally want to nominate...
Ja Yeon.
- Gosh. - For goodness' sake.
How could you seduce her with household appliances?
I've never seen anyone flirt with household appliances before.
What was that?
I want to give it to Sung Hwan as well.
- He dedicated so much time. - Seriously.
Sung Hwan came early in the morning...
- for preparations. - He worked hard.
Candidate one, Ku Sung Hwan.
- Candidate two, MINHO. - Okay.
Candidate 3, Ok Ja Yeon. Among the 3 candidates...
(I want you, MINHO.)
You can't win against him.
(Incredible recruiting ability and natural-born physique)
Sung Hwan worked hard.
- I know. - It was fun.
It was so much fun.
(Candidate 1, the captain of Team Ku, Ku Sung Hwan)
Baekdu ssireum champion.
They're showing this again.
That clip will be used often.
A runner's humiliation.
- MINHO was unrivaled. - That's right.
(The ace of super volleyball, Ok Ja Yeon Koung)
- She was like Kim Yeon Koung. - Ja Yeon did so well.
(She stayed consistent and brought good results to the team.)
She ran well too.
(Candidate 3, the best athlete among women, Ok Ja Yeon)
Candidate one, Ku Sung Hwan.
- Okay. - Candidate two, MINHO.
Candidate 3, Ok Ja Yeon. Among the 3 candidates...
Raise your hand for candidate one, Ku Sung Hwan.
Ja Yeon.
- Okay. - He did well.
Quite a few people voted for him.
- I wanted the captain to win. - Same here.
Thank you.
Next, MINHO.
This is meaningless.
It's MINHO.
Next, MINHO.
This is meaningless.
- It's MINHO. - He did very well.
- That's right. - He came from behind and won.
- It was impressive. - Candidate three, Ok Ja Yeon.
Of course.
Ok Ja Yeon.
- He's serious about her. - He's different.
He's serious about her.
He's persistent.
- She's sick and tired. - She's serious too.
She's serious too.
This isn't "I'm Solo."
He's a fool of love.
You don't hate it, do you?
I hate it!
- "I hate it!" - She held it in for a long time.
"I hate it!"
- "I hate it!" - Then...
(She feels relieved.)
Today's MVP is MINHO.
(Today's MVP, MINHO)
Fiery charisma, MINHO.
Thank you so much.
I wanted the Airwrap.
I'm jealous of the Airwrap.
I'm jealous.
- Seriously. - You get a vacuum cleaner too.
Thank you.
- He won all the prizes. - I was jealous.
- That's incredible. - I was jealous.
- Those who didn't get anything... - I'm glad that I worked hard.
Will get a towel as a souvenir.
Take one. Thank you for your hard work.
I knew that some people wouldn't win a prize.
- Here is a towel. - So I prepared some towels.
A participation prize is a must.
- The towel was cute. - Take a towel.
Gosh, there is embroidery too.
- This is the towel. - There is embroidery.
- Innocent Moo-ku. - The First...
- Innocent Moo-Ku Fall Field Day. - It's a souvenir.
It's like an alumni meeting.
- Seriously. - Such a souvenir is a must.
- It's atmospheric. - Such a souvenir remains.
- It's so cute. - It remains.
President Jun, thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Guys, let's clean up.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Let's clean up and go home. - Thank you for your hard work.
- Let's hurry up. - Together, it takes no time.
My feet are cold.
- He left his shoes there. - My goodness.
- Why did he wear those shoes? - Seriously.
Ji Hyeon is good.
(Rolling up)
Whose is this?
We cleaned up quickly.
- It was fun. - It was really fun.
(The fun field day ends.)
- It was fun. - It was so much fun.
(The field day began with the Moo-Ku duo's cute act.)
That day was so...
Everything happened in a day.
(They remained competitive all day long.)
(They shared emotions in a strange way.)
The Joseon butcher.
(There was happiness they couldn't hide.)
(They threw their bodies as much as they wanted.)
(It was a fall day.)
- It's a good memory. - I want to play volleyball again.
Let's do it again with a big ball.
Let's meet again at the Second Spring Field Day.
We enjoyed the video.
(It was fun.)
The First Field Day was very fun.
I don't know about anything else,
but Kian84 needs to get his revenge.
You can't leave it at that.
How will I beat him?
I can't imagine Kian84 beating MINHO in anything.
He's preparing for a triathlon.
You can do it.
- Show him the power of the 40s. - That's right.
- I can't play soccer. - You can beat him in baseball.
- Really? - You can beat him in baseball.
- Is he bad at baseball? - He's bad at baseball.
- Baseball is a good event. - Yes.
You want to choose a sport MINHO is bad at.
A sport he's bad at.
If we have the Second Field Day, you and MINHO should have...
- a match as the opening event. - That's right.
I'll plan it.
- Okay. - Okay.
- That's a good idea. - We can create a picture...
- we want. - That's right.
Let's do it on a nice spring day.
- That's a good idea. - Okay?
- Okay. - I want to see him shed tears.
- Due to feeling victimized? - Out of those clear eyes.
That's right.
- Welcome. - Welcome.
(Staring)
Why is CODE KUNST in that seat?
- Hold on. - Kian84 isn't here today.
- What happened? - Where did he go?
After losing in a race,
he went abroad to train.
- You mean the field day? - For real?
- Because of that loss? - Yes, he was so upset.
- He was very upset. - Seriously.
Hue Park, it has been a while. Welcome.
- Thank you. - How have you been?
(Last time, Hue showed his daily life in New York.)
I enjoyed watching his daily life in New York.
(A Korean musical that won 6 Tony Awards)
(The writer of "Maybe Happy Ending")
Hue Park.
(Seats continue to get sold out at Broadway.)
It's full.
It was unbelievable.
(Overcoming cultures and borders, people connected to the story.)
The musical brings tears to the eyes.
(Writer Hue Park)
- He shed tears. - Tears.
(I replayed this video many times. Hue Park made me emotional.)
It's his work.
Don't you hear...
the sound of someone sucking up?
- Mr. Suck-Up! - My goodness.
Mr. Suck-Up is here.
(Mr. Suck-Up, Kai is here.)
Hello.
(Kai gained energy by sitting next to Hue Park.)
(My eyes only see Hue.)
(Kai, )
(you're sucking up so much today.)
(That was how he became Mr. Suck-Up.)
(He had even prepared a serenade.)
He sat next to Hue.
- My goodness. - Kai, my goodness.
Are the two of you a pair?
Of course, I'm...
Hue's cutie, Mr. Suck-Up.
- Cutie? - Cutie?
That's who I am.
Upon hearing that Hue would be here,
I came to receive good energy.
Hue, how did people react to your appearance on the show?
I received many calls.
Wherever I go,
people give me matcha latte...
even before I order.
- So many people recognize me. - Really?
That's incredible.
It's time for the daily life of Hue Park.
The man Mr. Suck-Up has eagerly waited for.
Let's check it out.
(Another Happy Ending Today)
(Hue is sleeping with a sleep mask on.)
(Sleeping)
(The sound of the alarm notifies that morning has come.)
He wakes up at 7am.
(Not budging)
(Ringing)
What's wrong with that?
It feels like a horror movie.
It has to be thrown out once.
It has to be destroyed.
(Wriggling)
(Come here, alarm clock.)
(He barely manages to get up thanks to the intense alarm.)
But where is this place?
It feels quite different from his house in New York.
Right.
It doesn't feel like New York.
- It feels like a hotel. - Did he sleep in Ikea?
(Hue wakes up naturally in an unfamiliar place.)
(Drowsy)
(He tries to yawn away his sleepiness.)
(He does a simple face wash in the morning.)
(He then heads out of the restroom.)
- What? - Did you move?
His house...
This is Seoul.
I found a place to stay in Seoul.
(This is Hue's house in Seoul.)
Since he has a lot of work in Seoul as well.
For the past few years,
I've spent my time in Seoul in hotels for up to half a year.
That was why I got a house in Seoul as well.
- It feels different here. - Right.
As I couldn't change the wallpaper or flooring,
I went with black and white to suit the place.
I tried to add a bit of colors...
- that pop out... - Like that?
Throughout the house.
- I added just a bit of color. - Just a little.
Not too much.
It hasn't been a month since I got this place.
There are still many places that feel empty.
I also moved in with just a single suitcase.
(That's why there are a pile of items bought.)
I have a lot of things that I am missing,
so I am getting them one by one.
I'm still getting used to the place as well.
It's like starting to live alone all over again.
- Gosh. - Right.
I went to New York last week as well.
I go back and forth whenever I have work.
I've been busy with things like interviews these days.
(Winner of Asia Game Changer Award)
Right. He won a lot of awards too.
("KOCCA Seminar with Hue Park Successful")
("Literature Week 2025 Opens, First Day with Hue Park")
Gosh, he did a lot including lectures.
I feel happy even though I'm busy.
It's a chance to meet many different people.
I've only been writing at home,
but there's a certain energy that can be felt from people.
I feel careful to ask, but did you get your pay?
- It seems like he did. - Well,
I got part of it.
No wonder. He seemed to have gotten a new jacket.
- His necktie is made of leather. - Gosh!
- Earlier, - Not everyone can wear that.
His face glowed during the interview.
- Right. - That's the pay glow.
- There was a glow. - Right.
(The glowing paid man)
I should get treated by him once.
"Get treated by him."
I'll make sure to treat all of you...
once I get everything.
I'll make sure to remember that.
(You're unbelievable.)
(He drinks a cup of cold water as soon as he wakes up.)
Alexa, play Glenn Gould.
(He asks the AI assistant for music just like in New York.)
(Dragging)
(He starts his morning routine just like always.)
He lives just like how he lived in New York.
I think that's important.
When you're still half-asleep,
are you able to read words?
I heard this from a professor.
Reading within two hours of just waking up...
is the best way your brain absorbs most of the book.
- Really? -Yes.
Alexa, what time is it?
The time is 7:36am.
(Getting up)
(It's time to work out according to his morning routine.)
(Even in New York, and even in Seoul, )
(I will always keep my routine.)
It's easy to become lazy about doing the same thing.
I can feel that my body feels different from not doing it.
(His simple morning workout routine is over.)
(I should wash up quickly.)
(He chooses his outfit after washing up quickly.)
- What? Hold on. - It's a suit?
It feels like he's going to work.
It's different from his usual style.
Right. It's different.
(A neat look unlike last time)
(He then opens the fridge.)
(It's quite packed.)
- Gosh. - A lot of things were bought.
(Rummaging)
(Grapefruit and apple)
(A pack of yogurt as well)
(He hurriedly eats while standing.)
(He also eats the apple while standing.)
I was in a hurry, so I couldn't even sit.
He feels like an office worker.
(He quickly finishes his meal while standing.)
(Rustling)
The food waste.
(He cleans up the food waste right away as well.)
(Opening)
The freezer.
Gosh, he really has adjusted.
It's put in the freezer.
The food waste can be thrown out however you want in the US, right?
It isn't like that.
- Sorry. - Do you know what it's like there?
- Do you know what it's like there? - I haven't been to the US.
I bought one of those.
- It's the... - The food waste disposer?
- food waste disposer. - That's the best.
- You should get him one. - Right.
Should I?
It's all for your good.
Got it.
- What's the point of just talking? - Got it.
- Right. - Send one to his place right away.
Hue seemed to lack a few things.
- He lives a minimal life. - He's missing a few things.
I will make sure to fill your house!
There are a lot of cheaper ones these days.
(It's kept in the freezer before Mr. Suck-Up gets him one.)
(Rushing)
(Let's get going.)
(He hurriedly leaves the house.)
- It feels like Korea right away. - It's Korea.
He feels like an office worker.
(Rushing)
(He moves into the crowd.)
(Okay. I'm good with time.)
(Yongsan Station)
(He came to Yongsan Station in the busy morning.)
Where is he going?
Yongsan Station is really busy.
(Crowded)
(He naturally joins in...)
(with the people getting to work.)
Our country's subway system is very convenient, isn't it?
- And it comes right on time. - Right.
- It's the best thing to have. - I got really surprised.
(Rummaging)
(He suddenly gets out a pen and notebook.)
(He starts writing something.)
This is what's good about using public transportation.
Throughout that long period of time,
it's nice that you can use it to prepare for something.
(He spends his time on the subway efficiently.)
It feels like New York with this scene.
Right.
I thought it was quite strange.
It was because there were a couple of foreigners.
I was wondering why it felt just like New York.
"Which one is New York?"
There are a lot of foreigners in Seoul.
- "Where is New York?" - The place where Hue Park is.
Right.
- What? - Goodness.
(Unable to believe what they just heard)
What was that about? "The place where Hue Park is?"
That is where New York is.
Mr. Suck-Up is at it again.
(Mr. Suck-Up is getting more expressive over time.)
(While Hue is making his surroundings feel like New York, )
(the subway heads further away.)
How far is he going?
This stop is Suwon.
- Suwon? - He went really far.
I was on the subway for over an hour.
- Right. That's far. - Right.
Gosh, there are a lot of people.
(He moves quickly in Suwon as well.)
(Running up)
(He heads somewhere in hurried steps.)
- Doesn't it feel like a school? - A school?
(Hue heads in somewhere after moving a long distance.)
(Cross-Culture Generation: Global Generation Storytelling)
(Hue Park)
Today, I'll be at Kyung Hee University...
for a lecture for the students.
I will talk about the things that I do.
I will be doing a lecture based on...
my tough times while being a college of arts student.
- They all want to hear from him. - This is a great time for them.
It's different when they come with their own dreams.
Their eyes will be shiny.
(The lecture hall gets filled as they wait for Hue.)
The title is all in English.
Cross-Culture Generation,
- Global Generation Storytelling. - What does that even mean?
- It's all in English. - What does that mean?
- Cross-Culture... - It means, "Let's do this."
- That's what it means? - "Let's do this."
"Let's do this."
How does that mean, "Let's do this?"
Why does that have to sound so hard?
You're looking down on us so much.
(Are you looking down on us?)
- He's cheering up the next gen. - Is that so?
- Right. - I see.
(Hue has come to cheer up the students.)
(Drinking water)
(He continues to drink the water.)
I'm really nervous right now.
- It seems like it. - Right.
Out of all lectures,
lectures for students are the toughest.
It's because a single thing that you say...
- is able to... - There's a big responsibility.
Right. It's able to change their lives.
That is why you feel hesitant to say things.
He's a bit like Kai.
- He's a professor. - Right.
(Professor Kai feels proud.)
Everything is ready.
- You may head in now. - Right.
- Should I head in now? - Yes.
(Unlike his voice, his face looks very nervous.)
(Let's go, Hue!)
Please give him a warm welcome.
Here's Writer Hue Park!
(Here's Writer Hue Park!)
- There are a lot of them. - There are a lot of them.
Gosh!
There were around 300 students.
(The students welcome him with a round of applause.)
- A lot of them have come. - Gosh.
(Smiling)
(Holding her hands tight)
This is exciting.
Hello, everyone. I'm a musical writer,
lyricist, and director.
My name is Hue Park. It's a pleasure to meet you.
(It's a pleasure to meet you.)
The atmosphere feels great.
(Feeling relieved by the great atmosphere)
It's been a while since I visited a school campus,
and it feels very exciting.
It reminded me a lot about my past.
I've been here 20 years ago.
That was why I felt excited on my way here.
(Feeling nervous)
First of all, I have a question for all of you.
- What? - "After..."
(He opens up his notebook with his shaky hands.)
"finishing my studies,"
"I feel certain about what I will do in the future."
Can I see a raise of hands for those who feel this way?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight...
There seems to be only around ten people.
I think I've done a good job to come here.
It's because I was just the same...
as those who didn't raise their hands.
(I didn't feel certain about my future, like most students.)
I've changed my major twice.
I've attended two schools.
In both schools, I felt that I was someone...
that was quite distant from the mainstream.
"Where will a person like me feel welcomed?"
"Why am I trying to become an artist?"
I really struggled with these thoughts...
during my 20s.
I'm saying this for those who might be thinking the same.
I wanted to tell you...
that I felt lost for a long time...
like all of you.
I graduated from an art high school...
and entered an art university.
It was really hard to enter,
but once I got in, I felt lost about...
what I was going to make a living with.
- That's how it feels in that field. - It feels vague.
Right.
But when a successful senior...
who studied the same major says something like that,
- you would feel very grateful. - Right.
- Seriously. - You would feel hope.
Your own tastes are very important.
No matter how pathetic people say you are,
you must know what your tastes are...
and continue to develop them.
I don't think following a trend...
is what an artist does.
My gosh!
You're definitely not an artist.
(The trend hunter suddenly makes an appearance.)
I've never been surprised before after seeing my face.
- What was that? - Well,
I see that as a form of art in this generation.
Right.
(Maesaengi Art, Jun Hyun Moo, 2025)
The sense of emptiness from trends.
That was what I expressed.
I don't think following a trend...
is what an artist does.
A person who endlessly thinks about their philosophy...
and creates a trend.
- That is an artist. - The one who creates a trend.
You must not become people who follow trends.
I think that is what an artist must do.
I did a lecture for about 40 minutes...
while explaining my timeline.
I wandered around here and there and spat out a lot of things.
I'll stop speaking now.
Since I'm here,
feel free to ask me questions.
- The Q and A session. - That's the best part.
Shall we use this time for some questions?
Do you have any questions for me?
(Raising their hands right away)
- They responded right away. - I got so surprised.
- Many of them raised their hands. - Right.
That means they enjoyed the lecture.
(Beaming)
Yes.
The student in the black outfit.
I heard you worked as a designer in an advertising agency...
and wrote at night.
I want to ask if you had any difficulties...
while making money and being an artist.
Well, it's the same for everyone.
We were all freelancers too.
There's nothing that can be done before you become famous.
You aren't able to make money with what you enjoy doing.
You can't sit around and do nothing.
Right.
Did you just answer her question?
- "Nothing can be done." - It's the same for everyone.
(She answered the younger one's question right away.)
You have to have two jobs. What else can you do?
That was a great answer.
You should do lectures as well.
- She's so straightforward. - Go for it.
- You should do lectures as well. - But...
people need to hear things like this as well.
- Right. - There's nothing you can do.
It's definitely hard to do your work...
while working at a company.
You should make sure to draw a line.
When you are at work,
you respect the tastes of the clients...
and respect the needs of your superiors.
When it was my day off or when I came back home,
I tried hard to respect my own tastes.
That's the right thing to do.
The one wearing the hoodie.
How would you define "good lyrics?"
How would you define that person?
I would like to ask how you get inspired...
to create your work.
I read that inspiration always comes at a specific time.
There is someone who said...
that it's a matter of whether you're sitting at your desk or not.
I read that from another writer.
(They work hard to take notes so they don't miss anything.)
They're taking notes as well.
It's very sad to let him go, but we must end things here.
Please give him another big round of applause.
Thank you, everyone!
They look very satisfied.
They enjoyed it.
(The lecture ends in great success.)
- Thank you for your effort. - Thank you.
(He heads to the lobby right after the lecture.)
Gosh!
(Please give us your autograph.)
- They all wanted an autograph? - As expected.
(Crowded)
(After the lecture, )
(the students all gathered in the lobby.)
(It suddenly feels like a fan autograph event.)
- What is your name? - I'm Jang Se Rin.
Thank you.
Right.
- Thank you. - I remember the time in New York.
When the actors and actresses left the theater,
- they signed autographs. - Right.
I remember when you quietly got out while they did that.
- I'm Jang Soo Min. - Soo Min?
To be honest, I'm not used to it.
It still feels awkward to sign autographs for someone.
Asking for my autograph...
makes me think that my lecture was meaningful.
I really enjoyed your shows.
I watched "Il Tenore" and "Maybe Happy Ending..."
and I cried during both of them.
I'll make sure to watch the show that will be out soon.
Thank you.
- This is for you. - Thank you.
I did eat,
- but I'll make sure to enjoy this. - Really?
Thank you.
- This is such a precious thing. - It's for you.
- Thank you. - It's a Labubu.
(Touched by their warmth from their gifts)
It should be checked if it's a fake one.
(Being jealous)
- Thank you! - Gosh, they're going wild.
(The students feel delighted by his heartfelt autograph.)
They look delighted.
I met the young students and they felt so cute and lovely.
They felt like babies to me.
Had I gotten married with my first love...
during my college days,
they would've been around the age of my son or daughter.
When I was around their age,
I used to transcribe Writer Noh Hee Kyung's scripts.
I went to the university campus that made me feel excited...
and I got so much energy from the students.
- I'm a big fan. - Thank you.
You did it for all of them?
- I'm a big fan. - Good luck with your work.
Thank you.
Actually, there was a question I wanted to ask.
You mentioned personal preferences earlier.
I wondered if I should try different things even if I don't like them...
- when I'm still in school. - Of course.
You should go to a gallery every week.
Check out nice design blogs.
Check out blogs like It's Nice That every day.
She studies visual design.
You should check out other people's work when you're a student...
even if it's not what you prefer.
Try things that aren't yours.
Try imitating others too.
Read philosophy books even if it's not your major.
See how the world works through newspapers.
Watch news as well.
The things you thought were never your taste...
somehow become your taste one day.
You should try everything...
- at that time. - That's right.
- Thank you. - Study hard.
(Hue answers even the last person's question with sincerity.)
Gosh, it's fall.
- Goodness. - Gosh, the campus is pretty.
Campuses are the best in fall.
I think the air on campus is different from outside.
Gosh, I feel so relieved.
- Thank you! - Thank you.
- Sure. - Thank you.
Bye.
- It's nice to see college students. - It gives you energy.
They really felt like my nephews and nieces.
And you'll meet one of them later in life.
- Right. - Actually, that's what they said.
"Let's meet on site."
- Such things are bound to happen. - That's right.
- "I was in that lecture hall." - Exactly.
Then you'd meet them.
It'd be really fascinating.
The weather is amazing.
(He finally sees the fall scenery after his tension eased.)
Look at the weather.
You're going to Seoul right away?
Yes, I had to...
What? He didn't go home.
- There were foreigners everywhere. - I know.
It feels like New York.
I feel like I'm seeing more than on "Surprise Mystery TV."
- Behind him... - There are definitely more...
- these days. - There are a lot these days.
- How can there be foreigners... - There are a lot.
- behind and next to him? - There are so many.
How is it possible when it's not even Itaewon Station?
Where did he go?
A cafe?
(Aladdin Used Bookstore)
Oh, it's Aladdin.
Aladdin?
It's a used bookstore I used to go often.
I used to go there during lunch break after having lunch...
and read books.
- "Books there were just sold." - Gosh, the books.
- Isn't that on Garosu-gil? - That's right.
I sold a lot of books there.
- When? - Then I might have your books.
You might. It feels really good when you earn two dollars...
after selling a book.
You went to sell your books, not buy?
I've never bought books from there.
You're so generous. You pay more for new books...
- and sell them cheap. - I drive the economy.
They pay you 3 dollars for books that cost 20 dollars.
- It's really infuriating. - He drives the economy?
- That'd be really neat. - To make money for valet parking.
There are so many people who sell books there.
Someone needs to sell their books...
- for others to buy them. - Mine were completely new.
I'd never even touched them.
- Completely new. - I see.
There are so many books...
- in great conditions. - Those are mine.
- They're really mine. - The good ones.
(Looking intently)
("Atonement")
Actually, just because books are a little worn...
doesn't mean they depreciate in value.
On top of that, they have books that went out of print.
There's a book that went out of print among the books I got today.
I think it's meaningful to get a book...
that holds someone's history.
It's fun to read sentences that are underlined.
It must be.
- Oh, you get such books there. - If you get books from there...
- The books with underlines. - Yes.
"Why did this sentence resonate with this person?"
It'd make me think about such things.
There's that kind of fun.
The moment you underline, the price plummets.
They check those?
They check everything.
- They do. - Really?
- What about dog-earing? - No.
That's not good. The price plummets.
Also, if there's a trace of food...
- Iffy ones like kimchi juice. - Yes.
Oh, if it's dirty?
- If it's dirty... - Then they don't accept it.
- They don't accept it? - They don't accept it.
They don't accept dirty ones.
My books have many pages with kimchi juice.
That's because you use them as a placemat.
- A placemat? - They don't accept one with a drop.
- They don't? - It was a big bummer.
If they don't find spots while flipping the pages,
they'd let it slide?
But they flip the pages ten times.
- "Rustling." - Gosh.
They'd flip pages like a machine.
"Rustling."
- They're different. - Of course.
- Well, they're there for that. - They're professionals.
(Staring)
(He takes a look at its cover...)
(and takes it as well.)
I don't really regret...
even if I buy books on impulse.
You see? You and I have a similar shopping style.
I buy many at once like that.
But he actually reads them.
I...
- They're completely new. - They're stuck together.
- Then you can get a good price. - Is that so?
Congratulations.
You should buy new ones and sell them there.
Yes, you should do that.
- If you have new books... - Please call me in advance...
- when you go sell your books. - That's right.
I'll get new ones and sell them right away.
You should drive the economy.
- I will. - Yes, you should drive it a lot.
I keep it moving big time.
I'm sorry, but there's a lot.
(Saving the Moomoo chance for another time)
(He bought 14 books.)
- Here you go. Thank you. - Thank you. Bye.
Goodbye.
(With both hands full with books)
(He heads straight home.)
Gosh, he has to unpack them.
I feel pressured every time I enter the house.
Maybe he won't be able to go out at one point.
(Striding inside past the boxes)
(Putting them down)
(Filling the empty bookshelf...)
(with the books he got today)
The empty bookshelf bothered me every time.
Oh, the bookshelf there is empty,
- come to think of it. - Right.
You need to fill it.
(Grabbing)
Yes, let's open them.
(Opening the boxes without getting changed)
(Rustling)
- That looks like a bulb head. - A lamp.
(Blue bulb head)
(Putting it in)
What?
They sell a lampshade...
that you can insert in that lamp.
- A customized one? - Yes.
I wanted to use blue as an accent color.
(Art school graduate Hue...)
(is good at color coordination.)
(Interior taste that reflects his expertise as a former designer)
That's a lamp too.
I got blue items separately.
(Putting it in)
That's fascinating.
I wanted the stand to be blue like the lampshade.
(Among various colors, )
Goodness.
(Hue's personal squares are blue.)
It's nice to fill the space with decorative objects.
You have a keen eye for color.
- It's stylish. - It's pretty.
(Putting the blue frame on the floor)
(Keeping other objects in neat white except for accent objects)
I think it's important to decorate the space you're often in.
- That way, you grow fond of it. - That's right.
That's nice.
I like its mood.
(Heading to the kitchen after decorating)
(Rummaging through something without even getting changed)
(Pulling something out)
(Adding a handful of pasta noodles)
(Prepping cherry tomatoes as well)
Alexa, what's the time?
It's 6:07pm.
(Heading to the front door after checking the time)
What's that?
Yes, that's how you become when you live in Korea.
Getting quick deliveries.
Gosh, I'm so tired!
- There's another one? - What did he order?
The packages were piled up outside.
(There are still a lot of packages left.)
There's no end to opening packages.
(Hurrying)
It was my first time cooking at the new place,
so I had to order the things I needed one by one.
That's right.
Alexa, what's the time?
It's 6:15pm.
(He keeps checking the time while opening the packages.)
That takes up all the time.
It took really long to open everything.
(Rushing)
- Gosh, that looks fresh. - He makes it proper.
Alexa, what's the time?
It's 6:24pm.
(Quickly shaking the salad out of the bag)
- Oh, you had food delivered too. - Oh, it's sushi.
He's fast.
Someone must be coming.
He made a lot.
- That's a lot for one. - Yes, it is.
Who could it be?
Who is it?
It's me.
- What? - Come in.
What? It's a woman.
(Smiling widely)
The door is open.
(Opening)
Hi.
- Hi. - Who are they?
- Why are you dressed like that? - Sorry.
- Will! - I knew it. It's Jin Joo.
- Park Jin Joo? - Oh, my.
(Songwriter Will Aronson and Actress Park Jin Joo)
Jin Joo is getting married.
- With who? - Really?
Who else? A man, probably.
- How would we know? - She's getting married?
The guests I invited for today's housewarming...
My partner who can't be separated from me...
and also my enemy, Will Aronson.
Actress Park Jin Joo, whom I've been working...
on a musical together for two years,
came to my housewarming, which I'm grateful for.
(Songwriter Will won the Tony Award with Hue.)
(Korean skills that surprised everyone)
(She drew much attention...)
(with her hyper-realistic acting of a nurse.)
(They've been working together since "Maybe Happy Ending.")
She's the lead of my musical.
That's right.
Will came to Korea to prepare...
"Maybe Happy Ending" in Korea with me.
- So he came also. - We see each other every day...
in the practice room, actually.
We're really comfortable with each other.
- You look really comfortable. - You become really close...
after doing a show together. You must know.
We become like family.
Goodness.
Wait.
Come on in.
- Hue. - Yes?
Aren't you dressed too nicely?
You think so?
I gave a lecture at a college.
- You had a lecture today? - Yes.
So I had to wear a tie too.
Are you good at cooking too?
It's pasta, and it's gluten-free.
You can eat it too, Will.
Will is allergic to flour. He's allergic to gluten.
- I was scooping it... - Oh, dear.
Look at him.
You came when I was plating it.
Since you guys are here anyway, I won't be pretentious.
- Let's scoop it from here. - Shall we?
Yes.
(Taking a glance)
(They naturally look around the house.)
Mother?
Hue, you're going to put these here for good, right?
(Magazines filled with Hue's face)
That's a nice magazine. They had us too.
- They embraced us. - That's right.
They embraced Jang Woo too.
(It wasn't easy to take his body profile photos.)
(They embraced all kinds of bodies.)
It left lasting memories for many people.
- That's right. - A kind-hearted magazine.
Until I find the right spot...
You'll leave them here...
- until you turn 50, right? - No.
"I'm so cool."
- "I'm the best. I'm Hue." - "I'm cool."
You're teasing me as soon as you're here.
I should continue cooking. You guys hang by yourselves.
But they turned out really nicely.
Hold on. I'm sorry. I'm almost done.
You should go in first.
- Gosh. - Oh, gosh.
The Tony Award is there.
Gosh, it's my first time seeing it.
- Can I touch it? - I also...
Can we touch it?
- He's not here. We can touch it. - Hue.
It's heavy, right?
Goodness.
Does it feel real?
- It still doesn't. - Still?
No.
Which year were you born, Will?
- I was born in 1981. - What was that?
You were born in 1981?
Why? Why is that funny?
I'm quite old, right?
- No. - I'm past my prime.
How does he know that expression?
- Who told him that? - It's such an advanced expression.
He learns weird expressions from somewhere and uses them on me.
Will said he had past his prime.
It's just the beginning for Will. He's not past his prime.
- Am I passing my heyday now? - Not at all.
Will, your prime is now.
It's now.
(Let's eat first.)
- Yes. - Since this looks the sloppiest,
- Not at all. - I'll have it.
Let's sit on the floor.
- Since I live alone, - You're right.
So I have only one chair for myself.
I'm sorry. I don't have any big tables at home, so...
- Not at all. Yes, it's fun. - This is more fun.
- It feels like a picnic. - Right.
It looks fun.
(Hue's one-pan pasta is done.)
You should get a foldable table or something.
If anyone drops that on the carpet...
- It'll get really awkward. - That's right.
And squashing anchovies on it.
They could squash them on the carpet as they sit.
- Cheers. Thanks for coming. - Cheers.
- Thank you for inviting us, Hue. - Not at all.
It's my first time eating the food you cooked.
You two are the first proper guests I've had over.
- Can I try it now? - Can I try it now?
- First time eating what you cooked. - I'm really worried.
I think it'll be really bad.
I made it after a really long time.
- It looks really good. - It's totally ruined.
(Exclaiming)
It's really good.
I like it. I love it.
- I'm not kidding. - I'm glad it suits his palate.
At least one of you likes it.
(Jin Joo takes a bite too.)
(Exclaiming)
- Hue. - I really like it.
I really like it.
Thank you for eating it so well. I didn't expect it.
- Hue, it's really good. - It's really good.
There's a lot more.
- That's good. - You can eat a lot.
- I can eat a lot. - You don't have to save it.
Okay.
- Gosh, he must've starved. - Goodness.
- He eats it like it's a snack. - Tell me about it.
It must suit his palate.
He scraped the plate clean.
Hue, thank you so much.
Thank you so much.
By the way,
Will will return to New York someday.
Hue, you will go back and forth, right?
Right. We're returning to New York right after the show.
Yes.
It makes me sad to think about parting with you two.
Will, you told me this.
That you think I will be a good elder.
- What's that supposed to mean? - That's...
- Will told me this. - I didn't mean me.
"Jin Joo, I think you'll be a good elder."
He said, "Jin Joo, I think you'll be a good elder."
I wanted to tell you that I wished...
we could be friends 10 or 20 years later.
- I see. You mean later. - I just meant...
"You'll be a good elder."
I think I get what he means.
But the word you used, "elder,"
made me look forward to getting older.
For the first time.
Then I'm glad.
(Touched)
- A good elder. - It's not easy to be one.
- A good elder. - There are times...
when the expressions they use when they're unsure...
- resonate with me more. - That's right.
Will, I think you know more vocabularies than us.
When you learned Korean for the first time,
didn't you say you learned...
- through songs? - Yes, I learned through songs.
- What kind of songs? - I learned through songs.
- Yes. - Which songs were they?
- "Aside." - "Aside."
- What? - Through a song called "Aside?"
- Really? - "Aside."
- "Aside." - "Aside."
- Through a song called "Aside?" - What?
- "Aside." - Really?
He sings that song every day.
- "Aside?" - Our song?
- Yes. - That's right.
He listened to SHINee's album every day...
and studied Korean.
- Really? - That's fascinating.
- That's amazing. - He's a total fan.
- You must feel proud. - I wasn't thinking much,
but suddenly, I want to be Mr. Suck-Up.
I want to be Mr. Suck-Up.
(Oh, gosh)
Does it make him Aside Mr. Suck-Up?
- Aside Mr. Suck-Up. - Aside Mr. Suck-Up?
How did you learn that song?
- Well, I just... - Did you teach him that song?
- No. - I don't think I did.
When Will first began studying Korean,
SHINee was really popular.
(SHINee's "Aside" moved the hearts of many people in 2013.)
- I heard it was one of the songs... - That's right.
That your fans liked.
Do you still remember the song?
(All night, I draw out your face)
(He starts singing right away.)
(Surprised)
(Although you won't know)
(Vocalizing)
He's so good.
(I'm scared that my held-in feelings will be noticed)
He remembers all the lyrics.
(It's started.)
Gosh, why am I embarrassed?
(Here comes the climax.)
(It's the hardest for me)
They know how to have fun.
(She gets excited as well.)
He's singing in perfect pitch.
He's a songwriter, after all.
(I know I can't)
(But I want to hold you)
This scene is so fascinating.
But I want to hold you
My energy was getting drained real-time.
(I want to dream with you)
- You're really good. - Yes, he's really good.
How can he remember everything?
The song dynamic control is right on point.
Gosh, I'm so drained.
You need to have extroverts around.
- That's right. - You need the energy.
Hue always gets his energy drained when he's with us.
Actually, my energy does get drained.
"Get drained."
Why does it mean a flag is waving?
Oh, he could've heard it as "flag waving."
- Oh, my. - Oh, a flag.
So your flag is waving?
How should we put that?
You can say "drained."
- A flag is waving. - It means my energy is drained.
I feel like you are...
- sucking my energy. - That's right.
- My energy is being drained. - Oh, as in "energy."
- "Energy." - A flag.
A flag is waving.
(Perfect teamwork)
This drains my energy as well.
I'm grateful for my life...
where I can travel back and forth between New York and Seoul.
But it's true that I get too busy and tired.
I get really lonely and depressed...
especially when I have to go to the airport at night.
When I travel back and forth.
Still, I got to meet young students...
at an unfamiliar place,
buy books,
and decorate my work space.
I had a housewarming for the first time too.
In two great cities,
Seoul and New York,
I have a place for myself and work as well.
I'm really grateful for it, and I'm really glad too.
It was a really fulfilling day.
Although I'm alone,
I was happy because I could be with others too.
- Congratulations on living alone - Congratulations on living alone
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
- Shall I blow them? - Make a wish first, shall we?
(Next story)
(Someone running with heavy breaths)
(And it's...)
(Hyun Moo?)
(I, Moomoo, )
(am joining the running craze.)
(The members who enjoy running every day)
(I, Moomoo, will join as well.)
(The so-called Moomoo's Fun Run)
(Searching far and wide for the hottest gear)
(It's only fun if you have hip gear.)
(We root for you, Moorathoner.)
(It's only fun if you receive enthusiastic support.)
(You got this!)
(I didn't know such a place existed in Seoul.)
(Congratulations on your marriage.)
(It's only fun if you run around the popular places.)
(Eating as he runs)
(It's fun to replenish my energy in a customized way.)
(Salute!)
(It's been two hours since he started running.)
(You lose track of time...)
(with Moomoo-style fun run.)
(Welcome to the Fun Run World)
(To welcome fall, Ja Yeon left for...)
(A recreational forest?)
(Recreational Forest)
(I came to go backpacking in nature.)
(Gosh, it smells nice.)
(Grunting)
(I can't go on.)
(I should rest.)
(I can't go on again. I should rest again.)
(Flopping down again)
(I should rest five more times.)
(I just want to stay lying here.)
(But still, let's do this.)
(Heave-ho)
(Amazed)
(Today's backpacking spot)
(Swift)
(Ja Yeon is happy in nature.)
(Shall I show my skill?)
(She's making red bean kalguksu.)
(Taking a bite)
(It was disastrous.)
(It's the taste of nature.)
(I Am Natural Ok Ja Yeon)